here's what's coming up in the category
このカテゴリで今後予定されているものは次のとおりです
five TV newsroom Raspberry Pi for having
5つのテレビニュースルームRaspberry Pi
problems with Wi-Fi when connected to
接続時のWi-Fiの問題
High Definition displays someone
高解像度は誰かを表示します
pretended to be mayor and the government
市長と政府を装った
gave him a dot-gov domain google has
グーグルが持っているドット政府ドメインを彼に与えた
confirmed that a flaw that allowed
許可した欠陥
hackers to take control of Android phone
ハッカーがAndroidフォンを制御する
cameras microphones and GPS locations
カメラマイクとGPSロケーション
without the owner's permission has been
所有者の許可なしに
fixed and a Smart Watch advertised as a
修正され、スマートウォッチが
way to help parents keep track of their
両親が彼らを追跡するのを助ける方法
children and give them peace of mind can
子供たちと彼らに心の平和を与えることができます
be turned into a frightening
恐ろしくなる
surveillance device stick around the
監視装置は
full details are coming up later in the
詳細については、
show this is the category-five TV
これがカテゴリー5のテレビであることを示す
newsroom covering the week stop texting
週停止テキストメッセージをカバーするニュースルーム
with a slight linux bias
わずかなLinuxバイアスで
I
私
sascha Rickman joined this week by Jeff
sascha RickmanがJeffによって今週参加しました
Weston all right some quick honorable
ウェストン大丈夫いくつかの迅速な名誉
mentions this week Google wants to bring
今週の言及は、Googleがもたらすことを望んでいる
Android as close as possible to the
Androidにできるだけ近い
mainline Linux kernel a new breed of
メインラインLinuxカーネルの新種
arm-based smartphones including the
を含むアームベースのスマートフォン
Librium 5 and the pine phone are
Librium 5と松葉は
targeting mainline Linux support as a
メインラインLinuxサポートをターゲットとして
feature and Google is clearly thinking
機能とGoogleは明らかに考えています
along the same lines
同じ線に沿って
switching Android to run on the machine
Androidをマシンで実行するように切り替える
line Linux kernel would be a huge
ラインLinuxカーネルは巨大になるだろう
undertaking one that would inevitably
必然的に1つを引き受ける
require major technical and political
主要な技術的および政治的要求
changes to the way that the Linux kernel
Linuxカーネルの方法の変更
is currently developed instead of each
現在、それぞれの代わりに開発されています
Android device shipping its own device
独自のデバイスを出荷するAndroidデバイス
specific Linux kernel Google's idea is
特定のLinuxカーネルGoogleのアイデアは
to upstream as much code as possible in
できるだけ多くのコードをアップストリームに
short as reporter rana Amedeo sums up
記者ラナアメデオが要約するように短い
Google wants to decouple the Linux
GoogleはLinuxを分離したい
kernel from its hardware support and
そのハードウェアサポートからカーネル
Apple will have to face the law for it
Appleはそのための法律に直面しなければなりません
distributing crappy keyboards love it
くだらないキーボードを配布するのが大好き
Apple has been trying to stop a
Appleは
class-action lawsuit over faulty MacBook
欠陥のあるMacBookに対する集団訴訟
keyboards Federal Judge Edward Davila
キーボード連邦判事エドワード・ダビラ
has tossed out the attempt the lawsuit
訴訟を投げ出した
accuses Apple of not only hiding the
Appleを隠すだけでなく
fragility of MacBook butterfly'
MacBook蝶のもろさ」
keyboards but also failing to provide an
キーボードだけでなく、
effective fix or full compensation for
効果的な修正または完全な補償
customers who paid for repairs
修理代を支払ったお客様
the lawsuit covers many Apple laptops
訴訟は多くのアップルのラップトップをカバーしています
with butterfly keyboards starting with
バタフライキーボードで始まる
the original 12-inch MacBook from 2015
2015年のオリジナルの12インチMacBook
and including MacBook Pro models
MacBook Proモデルを含む
produced in 2016 and later let's get
2016年以降に制作された
into the stock top stories for following
フォローするためのストックトップストーリーに
this week raspberry pi 4 are having
今週のラズベリーパイ4は
problems with Wi-Fi when connected to
接続時のWi-Fiの問題
High Definition displays can't connect
高解像度ディスプレイが接続できない
your raspberry pi 4 to Wi-Fi try a lower
Wi-Fiへのラズベリーパイ4
resolution or a different HDMI cable
解像度または別のHDMIケーブル
developer andrey Kozeny reported quote
開発者andrey Kozenyが引用を報告
if the Raspberry Pi 4 outputs HDMI at a
Raspberry Pi 4がHDMIを出力する場合
resolution of 2560 by 1440 the Wi-Fi
2560 x 1440のWi-Fiの解像度
stops working end quote
終了引用符の動作を停止します
others have noted that the loss of 2.4
他の人は、2.4
gigahertz Wi-Fi when using just 1080p
1080pのみを使用する場合のギガヘルツWi-Fi
resolution but were able to solve it by
解像度が解決することができました
switching to the 5 gigahertz band there
そこで5ギガヘルツ帯域に切り替えます
are reports that Wi-Fi performance is
Wi-Fiパフォーマンスが
significantly degraded with monitors
モニターで著しく劣化
connected to HDMI 0 there is less
HDMI 0に接続されている
degradation
劣化
when the monitor is connected to HDMI
モニターがHDMIに接続されている場合
one if you're experiencing this problem
この問題が発生している場合
the current recommendation is to use the
現在の推奨事項は
HDMI port the lowest resolution possible
HDMIポートは可能な限り低い解像度
do not use Wi-Fi or wait for the next
Wi-Fiを使用したり、次の
hardware iteration that will hopefully
うまくいけばハードウェアの反復
fix the issue oh dear I got I got a say
問題を修正します。
I mean I've never been a fan of
私は一度もファンになったことがありません
Raspberry Pi Wi-Fi plain and simple so
Raspberry Pi Wi-Fiプレーンでシンプル
if I was using it as a multimedia PC I'm
マルチメディアPCとして使用していた場合
gonna go with Ethernet anyways
とにかくイーサネットで行く
especially now that they've got kik
特に今、彼らはkikを持っているので
event but to think that now there's this
イベントですが、今これがあると思う
issue that's cropped up and it's
問題が発生し、それが
surprising that it didn't come up before
それが前に現れなかったことに驚く
now because Raspberry Pi 4 has been
Raspberry Pi 4は
marketed as being like the desktop PC of
デスクトップPCのようなものとして販売
SBC's and of course the home theater PC
SBCともちろんホームシアターPC
of SBC's as well that's how they've
SBCも同様です。
marketed marketed it even though there
市販されていても
are more powerful boards out there but
より強力なボードがありますが、
Wi-Fi is kind of critical when you're
Wi-Fiは、あなたが
doing a home theater PC it really is and
ホームシアターPCをやっている
I mean this isn't an interesting problem
これは興味深い問題ではないということです
to have where it's based on a specific
特定の場所に基づいて
port that's video based I mean we're
ビデオベースのポートです
talking HDMI but suddenly when you're
HDMIを話しているが、突然
running at a really high resolution it
本当に高解像度で実行しています
kicks out your Wi-Fi and only on a
Wi-Fiをキックアウトします
certain band
特定のバンド
it feels - it feels to me like
それは感じている-それは私に
interference which is like isn't this
のような干渉はこれではありません
FCC compliant like that's that's how it
そのようにFCCに準拠している
feels to me it should be but I mean
私はそれがあるべきだと思うが、私は意味する
there's been a number of issues now with
今では多くの問題がありました
the Raspberry Pi 4 and it makes me
Raspberry Pi 4
wonder like how did this stuff get
このようなものはどうやって得たのだろうか
missed in the QC aspect of it yeah
QCの面で見逃した
certainly the USBC issue comes to mind
確かにUSBCの問題が頭に浮かぶ
where it's not a compliant USB C port
準拠のUSB Cポートではない場合
right that's a big problem so you have
それは大きな問題ですので
to have specific cables in order to
特定のケーブルを使用して
charge or to power it is this a newly
充電するか電源を入れるのはこれです
developing problem like will they be
彼らがするような問題を開発
able to fix it with an upgrade then or
アップグレードで修正できるか、または
you know I don't know sash I it seems to
あなたは私がサッシを知らないことを知っています
me like like I say it sounds like an
私のように聞こえます
interference issue which sounds like
ように聞こえる干渉の問題
something that they would have to do
彼らがしなければならないこと
hardware improvements in order to fix
修正するためのハードウェアの改善
that and I don't know that it's a new
それと私はそれが新しいことを知りません
issue it's just that somebody finally
問題は最終的に誰かが
made the connection that the Wi-Fi
Wi-Fi
dropping out is
ドロップアウトは
with regards to to the HDMI output as
HDMI出力に関して
you mentioned somebody had noticed that
あなたは誰かがそれに気づいたと言いました
if you switch to five gigahertz versus
5ギガヘルツに切り替えると
2.4 gigahertz it seemed to have better
2.4ギガヘルツの方が良いように見えた
connectivity when you're connected to
接続時の接続性
HDMI so really I mean it's actually a
HDMIなので、実際には
good news story that if all of them were
それらすべてが
having this problem at least there's a
少なくともこの問題を抱えている
bit of a workaround oh sure right yeah
回避策の少しああそうそうそう
yeah but then you do lose one out like
ええ、しかしあなたは1つを失います
you're now missing out on an HDMI port
あなたは今、HDMIポートを逃しています
on your bike yeah you are so yeah and
あなたの自転車でそうだね
there's a fine line I mean I think with
細かい線があります
single board computers - we there there
シングルボードコンピュータ-そこにある
are two sides of the user base there's
ユーザーベースの2つの側面があります
the side that I am which is I know that
私がいる側は私が知っている
it's a single board computer I feel like
それは私が好きなシングルボードコンピュータです
it's groundbreaking and earth-shattering
それは画期的で大破です
and the technology has been condensed
技術は凝縮されています
from the supercomputer into a
スーパーコンピューターから
pocket-sized device and I'm so impressed
ポケットサイズのデバイスと私はとても感銘を受けました
and if there's problems I'm okay with
そして問題がある場合は私は大丈夫です
that and I'm like I didn't pay a lot for
それと私は多くを支払わなかったようです
this and it's like I'm like on the
これと、それは私がのようなものだ
bleeding edge of what is next and then
次のものの最前線
there's the other side that's like I
私のような反対側があります
bought this to have two 4k video outputs
これを購入して、2つの4kビデオ出力を用意しました
and if I connect them I can't work the
そして、私はそれらを接続する場合、私は働くことができません
Wi-Fi right and that's the flip side of
Wi-Fiの権利とそれの裏返し
it and I can understand that side of it
それと私はその側面を理解することができます
as well especially for the non techie
特に技術者以外の人にとっても
the non tinkerer right I'm a tinkerer I
私はいじくり回しているよ
want to play around I don't I don't mind
遊びたい気にしない
if things don't always work the way
物事がいつもうまくいかない場合
they're supposed to because I love to
私がするのが好きだから
tinker and I love I'm gonna be the one
いじくり回し、私は私が1つになるのが大好き
who buys the next gen because I want to
私がしたいので、誰が次の世代を買います
see how it how it progresses and you and
それがどのように進行するかを見て、あなたと
you know because you know that they
あなたは彼らが知っているので知っています
really want excellence that they're just
彼らはただの卓越性を本当に望んでいる
gonna push in and make it better for the
押し込み、より良くする
next gen yeah absolutely but there's
ええ絶対に次世代ですが、あります
this fine line also with the development
開発にもこの細線
process and the creation of the product
プロセスと製品の作成
where they're trying to drive down the
彼らが追い払おうとしているところ
price to 25 $35 and if they're gonna do
25ドル35ドルの価格と彼らがやるつもりなら
that with to 4k outputs and better Wi-Fi
4k出力とより良いWi-Fi
and USBC like they're cutting corners
そしてUSBCは、彼らが角を切っているように
folks like you know they are cutting
あなたのような人々は彼らがカットしていることを知っています
corners like crazy to make this thing
このようなものを作るのに夢中のようなコーナー
happen
起こる
so there's
だから
you know there you got it you got to put
あなたはそこにあなたがそれを手に入れたと知っています
things into perspective like that sure
そのような視点に物事を確かに
you win a little you lose a little yeah
あなたは少し勝ちますあなたは少しええ失います
someone pretended to be a mayor and the
市長のふりをして
government gave him a dot-gov domain a
政府は彼にドット政府ドメインを与えました
security researcher acquired an official
セキュリティ研究者が公式を取得しました
guv
グブ
to prove a suspected weakness in the
の疑いのある弱点を証明する
system which could have been used to
に使用できたシステム
spread fake emergency alerts or obtain
偽の緊急警報を広めるか、入手する
private information about citizens the
市民に関する個人情報
researcher posed as the mayor of a small
研究者は小の市長を装った
town with population of less than 6500
人口が6500人未満の町
people all they had to do was set up a
彼らがしなければならないのは
fake Google Voice number and gmail
偽のGoogle Voice番号とGmail
address both completely unaffiliated
完全に無関係の両方に対処する
with the town after that they filled out
その後、町で彼らは記入しました
an official authorization form which
公式の承認フォーム
basically asks for the same contact
基本的に同じ連絡先を尋ねる
information of registrar would require
レジストラの情報が必要になります
the documents needed to be printed on
印刷する必要がある文書
the town government's official
町政府の役人
letterhead which the researcher obtained
研究者が入手したレターヘッド
by searching for other official
他の役人を探す
documents posted by the town online
町がオンラインで投稿した書類
according to a town clerk from the
町の事務員によると
actual town the only inquiry the city
実際の町の唯一の問い合わせ市
received from the GSA came ten days
GSAから受け取った10日来ました
after the researchers fake registration
研究者が偽の登録をした後
was approved and the GSA only called
承認され、GSAは
after the security researcher revealed
セキュリティ研究者が明らかにした後
what they've done to a cyber security
彼らがサイバーセキュリティに対して行ったこと
reporter who then inquired about the
について尋ねた記者
domain in the short time they had the
短時間でドメインが
domain which has since been revoked the
その後取り消されたドメイン
researcher was able to sign up for
研究者はサインアップできました
Facebook's law enforcement subpoena
Facebookの法執行機関の召喚状
request system which provides law
法律を提供する請求システム
enforcement and government entities with
執行機関および政府機関
personal user records initially thought
最初に考えた個人ユーザーの記録
gov domain names were only available to
govドメイン名は
u.s. federal government institutions
米国連邦政府機関
they've since been opened up to state
それ以来、彼らは州に開かれました
and local governments at the end of
そして地方自治体は
October 2019 a bill was introduced in
2019年10月に法案が導入されました
Congress to improve oversight over
議会が監督を改善する
government domains by the cyber security
サイバーセキュリティによる政府ドメイン
and infrastructure security agency Wow
とインフラセキュリティ機関Wow
so they yeah Wow yeah yeah they did that
ええええええええ
like you would think if there's somebody
誰かがいると思うように
filling out an application for this
この申請書に記入する
before the approval goes in you start
承認が入る前に開始します
asking questions
質問する
but maybe we are we just a society that
でもたぶん私たちはただの社会で
relies so much on the information on the
の情報に大きく依存しています
internet that we believe what comes in
入ってくるものを信じるインターネット
an application for that is true yes and
そのためのアプリケーションはtrueです
now to be honest these dot of domain
正直に言うと、これらのドメインの点
names now that this stories come out
この物語が出てきた今の名前
would you then not trust like you should
あなたはあなたがそうするべきように信頼しないでしょうか
not trust them you know that people can
信頼できない
I don't know if you could say you can't
あなたができないと言うことができるかどうかはわかりません
trust them cuz I mean if I'm gonna go to
それらを信頼します。私が行くつもりなら
a doc of web site and I mean granted
Webサイトのドキュメントであり、許可されていることを意味します
they're mostly for like we said us and a
主に私たちが言ったように
lot of that isn't gonna apply
その多くは適用されません
necessarily for use here in Canada well
カナダでの使用に必要です
we we're here in Canada but remember
私たちはカナダにいますが、覚えておいてください
that most of our viewers are in the
ほとんどの視聴者は
United States even though we have your
米国はあなたがいるにもかかわらず
servers world yeah perspective sure you
サーバーの世界そうそう見通し
know and we have to be able to dress
知っていて、私たちは服を着ることができなければなりません
that this is trustworthy but I would
これは信頼できるが、私は
think like you're gonna know what you're
自分が何であるかを知っているように思う
looking for I mean it's not like you're
探している私はそれがあなたのようではないことを意味します
gonna randomly search up like hey this
このようにランダムに検索します
is no no dude we're taught to trust that
私たちはそれを信頼するように教えられています
the lock means that it's secure
ロックは安全であることを意味します
yes the.gov means that it's an official
はい、the.govは公式であることを意味します
government website right so so in this
政府のウェブサイトはまさにそうです
instance so could they not take the
インスタンスなので、彼らは取ることができませんでした
actual town website and create a
実際の町のウェブサイトと作成
phishing site that now collects your
現在あなたを収集するフィッシングサイト
information and gets you to fill in
情報を入力して入力する
forms that gives the hacker this was a
ハッカーにこれを与えたフォーム
security researcher but what if it was a
セキュリティ研究者が、もしそれが
hacker thing is that this this is a guy
ハッカーのことは、これは男だということです
just trying to expose the suspect ruling
疑わしい判決を暴露しようとしている
it can be done and he did prove it and I
それを行うことができ、彼はそれを証明し、私は
mean that's good that it it ended well
それはそれがうまく終わったことは良いことを意味します
but it could have ended badly and so
しかし、それはひどく終わったかもしれません
people need to maybe dial it back like
人々は多分次のようにダイヤルする必要があります
they opened up the dot-gov to maybe more
彼らは多分それ以上にドット政府を開いた
I guess more complacency by allowing
私は許可することにより、より満足していると思います
local government sure the scary thing
地方自治体は恐ろしいことを確信しています
about this and I mean maybe it wasn't
これについて、私は多分そうではなかったことを意味します
random but the fact that one of the
ランダムですが、
first things that this guy did was then
この男が最初にしたことは
get access to the Facebook information
Facebook情報にアクセスする
why not continue proving the point well
ポイントをうまく証明し続けてみませんか
exactly but I mean this this is then
正確ですが、これはこういうことです
gonna be one of those stories where
それらの物語の一つになります
people are gonna go Oh Facebook that's
人々はああFacebookに行くつもりです
you know it's like no no let's focus on
あなたはそれがノーだと思わないことを知っています
the real issue here like you you trusted
信頼できるあなたのようなここの本当の問題
something that became untrustable
信頼できないもの
yes untrustworthy whatever this
はい、これは信頼できない
reporters self-reported right like they
記者は彼らのように自己報告した
talk to a security expert right it
セキュリティ専門家に相談してください
wasn't like he went hey this is what
これは彼が行ったようなものではありませんでした
I've done like you spoke to somebody who
あなたが誰かに話しかけたように
then inquired that's the only reason
それが唯一の理由だと尋ねた
they found out didn't inquire how long
彼らはどのくらいの時間を尋ねなかったことがわかりました
could this have gone on I would have
これが続いていたかもしれない
liked to know I'm hot like I'm happy not
私は幸せではないように暑い知っているのが好き
to know really it would be scary but how
本当に知っているのは怖いけど
far could they have gone could to the
彼らはどこまで行けたのか
moon there's no answer there's no end
月は答えがない終わりがない
yeah it's it opens up the question how
ええ、それはどのように質問を開きます
many other fake Gove's are there out
他の多くの偽のゴーブがそこにあります
there yeah so be leery I suppose yeah
そこにうんざりするので
where we always have to be careful
常に注意しなければならない場所
always have to be careful folks we've
常に注意を払う必要があります
got to take a quick break the crypto
暗号を簡単に破る必要がありました
report and more of this week's top tech
今週のトップテクのレポートなど
stories are coming up don't go anywhere
物語が近づいているどこにも行かないでください
[Applause]
[拍手]
you
君は
welcome to the cryptic on my name is
私の名前の謎めいた世界へようこそ
Bart Koenig and I'm reporting to you
バート・ケーニッヒと私はあなたに報告しています
from Florida USA I've got into NASA
米国フロリダ州からNASAに参加しました
background and it's probably any year
経歴とおそらく一年
it's a European one I've been involved
それは私が関与してきたヨーロッパのものです
in this industry since 12 2015 and
2015年12月からこの業界で
occupied many roles starting with coding
コーディングから始まる多くの役割を占めた
running team supporting icos and like
ICOなどをサポートする実行中のチーム
most of us also losing money through
私たちのほとんどは、
trading tokens the crypto corner will be
暗号化コーナーの取引トークン
split in two parts the first one will be
最初の部分は2つの部分に分割されます
news so what happened during the last
ニュースだから最後の間に何が起こったのか
seven days and the second part will be
7日間と2番目の部分は
about special subject this time we'll be
今回は特別なテーマについて
talking about the private key so let's
秘密鍵について話しますので
dive into it the market cap of the
それの時価総額に飛び込みます
industry has not changed really changed
業界は本当に変わっていません
the last seven days there were some ups
最後の7日間、いくつかのアップがありました
and downs but it is hovering around 200
ダウンしますが、約200をホバリングしています
billion US dollars the Bitcoin market
10億米ドルのビットコイン市場
share is around 66% so those things
シェアは約66％です
haven't really changed what has changed
変わったことは本当に変わっていない
is some interesting news coming from
からの興味深いニュースです
several countries first one is India
いくつかの国は最初にインドです
India for the first time is committing
インドは初めてコミットします
to do some research on blockchain
ブロックチェーンに関するいくつかの研究を行う
technologies to establish a national
国家を確立するための技術
framework for blockchain technologies
ブロックチェーン技術のフレームワーク
which is great news because in the past
過去には素晴らしいニュースです
they have been very negative towards the
彼らは非常に否定的でした
crypto industry Germany starting with a
ドイツの暗号産業
new proposal law that would legalize
合法化する新しい提案法
banks being able to hold
保持できる銀行
cryptocurrencies in the past I had to go
私が行かなければならなかった過去の暗号通貨
through third parties also the holding
第三者を通じても開催
through third parties now they will be
サードパーティを通じて
hopefully soon allowed to hold them
うまくいけばすぐにそれらを保持することができました
themselves South Korea South Korea has
自分自身韓国韓国が持っています
been always very positive towards the
常に非常に前向きでした
crypto industry but they are now working
暗号業界ですが、彼らは今働いています
on a bill that will provide a legal
法律を提供する法案に
foundation for cryptocurrencies so
暗号通貨の基盤
that's going to be interesting because I
私は面白いので
said the leading edge and they they have
最先端を言って、彼らは持っている
been always very positive in this
これには常に非常に肯定的でした
industry other news is up it the
業界の他のニュースはそれまでです
exchange went through
交換が通過しました
was hacked last week and they stole 340
先週ハッキングされ340を盗んだ
mm ether those are known where they are
それらがどこにあるか、それらは知られています
so the wallets are known although what
財布は知られていますが
they don't know who the people are
彼らは人々が誰なのか知らない
behind them but remains to be seen what
それらの背後にあるが、何を見られるように残っています
will happen with those either the big
それらのいずれかで発生します
exchanges they all set they're not going
彼らはすべて彼らが行かないことを設定する交換
to trade those either into any other
それらを他のものに交換する
cryptocurrencies or interfered BitFenix
暗号通貨または干渉されたBitFenix
becomes the first major exchange to
への最初の主要な交換になります
enable Bitcoin lightning support which
ビットコイン稲妻のサポートを有効にします
is interesting because as you know
あなたが知っているように
Bitcoin lightning is the second layer
ビットコインの稲妻は2番目の層です
application on the Bitcoin platform
ビットコインプラットフォーム上のアプリケーション
which is equivalent to or they want to
それは同等または彼らがしたい
have it equivalent to a visa payment
ビザ支払いと同等のものを持っている
platform in regards to speed and also
速度に関してもプラットフォーム
fees and then balance is rolling out the
料金とその後のバランスがロールアウトされています
theorem futures so previously you could
定理先物
do trade only Bitcoin futures and now
現在はビットコイン先物のみを取引しています
you'll have also the possibility to
あなたにも可能性があります
trade in if your futures subject of the
あなたの先物が
week is the private key the private key
週は秘密鍵です秘密鍵
is an essential part of a cryptocurrency
暗号通貨の重要な部分です
and it ultimately defines who the owner
そして最終的に所有者を定義します
of a coin or token is let me give you an
コインまたはトークンの
example if you purchase some tokens
トークンを購入した場合の例
through an exchange and you leave them
交換を通じて、あなたはそれらを残します
on the exchange when those tokens are
それらのトークンが
not yours they belong to the crip to the
あなたのものではなく、彼らは
exchange only once you transfer those
それらを転送した後にのみ交換する
tokens over to your wallet like let's
のようにあなたの財布にトークン
say for example Exodus or treasure or
たとえば、出エジプト記や宝物、または
ledger and then those tokens will be
元帳とそれらのトークンは
yours and that's defined through the
あなたのものであり、それは
private keys I always make sure that you
秘密鍵私はいつもあなたが
are in possession of the private key and
秘密鍵を所有している
the easiest way to do that is through a
それを行う最も簡単な方法は
wallet like Exodus as mentioned Exodus
出エジプト記のような出エジプト記のような財布
treasure or ledger and that's it from me
宝または元帳、それは私からのそれです
so I'll see you next week and thank you
来週お会いしましょう
for watching thank you Robert and for
見てくれてありがとうロバートと
those of you watching we do not provide
ご覧の方は提供していません
financial advice about cryptocurrency
暗号通貨に関する財務アドバイス
this is more so just an FYI for you so
これはもっと参考になります
you know what's happening in the crypto
あなたは暗号で何が起こっているか知っています
markets
市場
Google has confirmed that a flaw that
Googleはその欠陥を確認しました
allowed hackers to take control of
ハッカーが制御できるようにした
Android phone cameras microphones and
Android携帯カメラのマイクと
GPS location without the owner's
所有者のいないGPSロケーション
permission has been fixed the flaw was
欠陥は修正されました
identified by security firm checkmarks
セキュリティ会社のチェックマークで特定
which found quote multiple concerning
複数の引用が見つかりました
vulnerabilities and quote in the Google
Googleの脆弱性と引用
camera app that enabled them to spy on
スパイを可能にしたカメラアプリ
its users the issue which also affected
そのユーザーも影響を受けた問題
Samsung meant that hundreds and millions
サムスンは何億という
of smartphone users were at risk
スマートフォンユーザーの
according to the firm its team found
そのチームが見つけた会社によると
that by quote manipulating specific
特定の操作を引用することで
actions and intents an attacker can
攻撃者ができるアクションと意図
control the app to take photos or record
アプリを制御して写真を撮ったり記録したりする
videos through a rogue application that
不正なアプリケーションを介した動画
has no permission to do so end quote
そうする許可がありません
check marks also found that certain
チェックマークも特定の
scenarios enabled hackers to access
ハッカーがアクセスできるシナリオ
stored videos and photos or to see GPS
保存されたビデオや写真、またはGPSを見る
metadata embedded in photos that would
写真に埋め込まれたメタデータ
locate a user the firm was able to
会社ができたユーザーを見つける
access these vulnerabilities using a
これらの脆弱性にアクセスするには
mock-up weather app that only required
必要なだけのモックアップ天気アプリ
basic storage permissions from an
からの基本的なストレージ許可
Android user according to the firm
会社によるとAndroidユーザー
storage permissions are very broad and
ストレージ権限は非常に広く、
give access to the entire SD card after
後にSDカード全体へのアクセスを許可する
identifying the flaw the firm notified
会社が通知した欠陥の特定
Google which after researching the
Googleが調査した後
report found that the vulnerabilities
レポートでは、脆弱性
were quote not specific to the pixel
ピクセルに固有ではない引用でした
product line and that the impact was
製品ラインとその影響は
much greater and extended into the
はるかに大きく、
broader Android ecosystem and quote the
より広いAndroidエコシステムと引用
tech giant has since fixed the
ハイテクの巨人はそれ以来修正しました
vulnerabilities and thanked the security
脆弱性とセキュリティに感謝
firm for identifying the issue Samsung
問題を特定するための会社サムスン
has also released patches to fix the
また、修正するパッチをリリースしました
issue since it was discovered that's a
それが発見されたので問題
scary story yes I mean I am always won
怖い話はい、私はいつも勝つということです
whenever I download an app I look at all
アプリをダウンロードするたびに私はすべてを見ます
the permissions and there are times
許可と時間があります
where if I'm looking at two different
私が2つの異なるを見ている場合
comparable apps yes you know in the
あなたが知っている同等のアプリはい
Android store will tell me what
Androidストアは何を教えてくれます
permissions doesn't require and I will
許可は必要ありません。
go with the one that has less access to
へのアクセスが少ない方に行く
my phone but I have noticed with the
私の電話ですが、私は
access to file storage that
ファイルストレージへのアクセス
is everything and that's been one of my
すべてであり、それは私の1つでした
chief complaints and I would love to see
主な苦情と私は見たいです
on a future update that access to
にアクセスする将来のアップデートで
storage permissions is broken down to
ストレージ権限は次のように分類されます
save only access only specific areas
特定の領域のみへのアクセスのみを保存します
like I would like to see more definition
もっと定義を見てみたい
with that so these kind of things
それでこういうもの
hopefully don't happen as often right so
うまくいけばそう頻繁には起こらない
yeah the park that's scary is the fact
ええ、怖い公園は事実です
that it would look like you're not
あなたがそうではないように見えること
giving that much permission it's just
それだけの許可を与えるだけで
for one thing right but the one thing is
一つのことは正しいが、一つのことは
everything yeah exactly and that's you
すべてはええ正確にそれはあなたです
know with all the apps that people are
人々がいるすべてのアプリで知っている
producing and I mean we just went
生産し、私たちはちょうど行ったことを意味
through this with my kids because I
これは私の子供たちと
found
見つけた
they've been downloading apps that I had
彼らは私が持っていたアプリをダウンロードしてきました
on their phones right why why and what
自分の携帯電話で
actually alerted us to it is my daughter
実際に私たちに警告したのは私の娘です
asked me I mean she's eight yeah she
私は彼女が8ええだという意味です
asked me to you know to do something on
何かをすることを知っているあなたに私に尋ねた
her phone with our dog and I pop like I
私たちの犬と彼女の電話と私は私のようにポップ
go to load the screen like full-blown on
本格的な画面をロードするために行きます
adult pictures from spyware no man using
使用していないスパイウェアのアダルト写真
this on her phone I'm going come on what
これは彼女の電話で
have you downloaded and and she's like
ダウンロードして、彼女は
oh I I thought like I didn't know and
ああ、私は知らないと思った
I'm like this is my daughter yes because
私はこれが私の娘のようです
of these apps that she's downloaded that
彼女がダウンロードしたこれらのアプリの
I we had no clue so I mean we've fixed
手がかりがなかったので、修正した
everything but I'm thinking come on like
すべてが、私はのように来ると考えています
we have to be more aware of what we
私たちは私たちの
download and there's so much stuff
ダウンロードして、たくさんのものがあります
within the app stores that just want
ただ欲しいアプリストア内
access to your fallen ancing yeah I have
あなたの落ちた踊りへのアクセス
found that week after week reading
毎週読んでその週を見つけました
stories like this I download a whole lot
このような話をたくさんダウンロードします
less I don't my device I yeah I know the
私は自分のデバイスを持っていません
ones I like and I trust I don't need to
私が好きなものと私はする必要がないと信じています
be entertained by my phone so I don't
電話で楽しまれるので
download entertaining apps for those of
の楽しいアプリをダウンロードする
you who are watching this on your phone
あなたの電話でこれを見ているあなた
ignore everything that she's saying but
彼女が言っていることはすべて無視しますが、
it's scary right because you see you
あなたが見えるので怖いです
know different apps are popping up in
さまざまなアプリがポップアップしていることを知る
the news and they're doing and they
ニュースと彼らがやっていると彼らは
could seem so benign but they're doing
良性に見えるかもしれないが、彼らはやっている
such harm
そのような害
yeah so I guess the best thing to do is
ええ、そうするのが一番いいのは
really just stay on top of
本当にただ上にとどまる
yeah well I mean I at least do what
ええ、私は少なくとも何をするのか
you're doing
あなたはやっている
read through what permissions right at
権限を読んでください
least do that and then also hope like
少なくともそれをしてから
for example this has been patched since
たとえば、これは
since it was the vulnerability was
脆弱性だったので
released right so you just had kind of
すぐにリリースされたので、
have to hope for the good at all okay a
良いことを願わなければなりません
SmartWatch advertised as a way to help
支援する方法として宣伝されているSmartWatch
parents keep track of their children and
親は子供を追跡し、
give them peace of mind can be turned
彼らに心の平和を与えることができます
into a frightening surveillance device
恐ろしい監視装置に
researchers at the av-test Institute
av-test Instituteの研究者
have uncovered gaping privacy and
ギャップのあるプライバシーを発見し、
security holes in the SMA - watch touch
SMAのセキュリティホール-ウォッチタッチ
dot - M - Smart Watch the security
ドット-M-スマートウォッチのセキュリティ
lapses are so severe that the
失効は非常に深刻であるため、
researchers were able to piece together
研究者はつなぎ合わせることができた
a snapshot of the life and daily habits
生活と日常生活のスナップショット
of a randomly selected ten year old girl
ランダムに選択された10歳の少女の
from Germany among other data the
他のデータの中でドイツから
Chinese made device exposed the girl's
中国製のデバイスは、女の子のを公開しました
name age place of residence where she
彼女が住んでいる名前年齢の居住地
spends most of her day and the route she
彼女の一日と彼女のルートのほとんどを過ごす
takes the researchers could even access
研究者がアクセスすることさえできます
the sound messages that were transmitted
送信された音声メッセージ
to her device and that's still not all
彼女のデバイスにそれはまだすべてではありません
they were even able to monitor her
彼らは彼女を監視することさえできました
real-time GPS position obviously the
リアルタイムのGPS位置は明らかに
security shut shortcomings didn't affect
セキュリティシャットの欠点は影響しませんでした
just that single device the team said it
チームが言ったまさにその単一のデバイス
could gain access to the location phone
ロケーションフォンにアクセスできます
number photos and conversations of well
番号の写真と会話
over 5,000 children and was quick to
5,000人以上の子供がいて、
note the number of affected users might
影響を受けるユーザーの数に注意してください
in fact be far higher the researchers
実際、研究者ははるかに高い
found that in addition to communication
コミュニケーションに加えて
with the manufacturers server being
製造元サーバーが
unencrypted the online interface of the
暗号化されていないのオンラインインターフェイス
manufacturers server was completely
メーカーのサーバーは完全に
unsecured leaving it entirely open to
安全ではないため、完全に開かれたままになります
external on author ID access
作成者IDアクセスの外部
unauthorized access although an
不正なアクセス
authorization token was generated to
認証トークンが生成されました
prevent unauthorized access the server
サーバーへの不正アクセスを防止する
does not validate it which essentially
本質的にそれを検証しません
means anyone with enough hacking skills
十分なハッキングスキルを持つ人を意味します
should have no problem in accessing user
ユーザーへのアクセスに問題はないはずです
IDs this allows potential attackers to
これにより、潜在的な攻撃者ができるID
have the same access that a parent would
親と同じアクセス権を持っている
have this lapse in security was found to
セキュリティのこの失効が発見されました
affect users in Germany Turkey Poland
ドイツトルコポーランドのユーザーに影響
Mexico Belgium Hong Kong Spain the
メキシコベルギー香港スペイン
Netherlands
オランダ
China Jeff you don't look pleased yeah I
中国のジェフ、あなたはうんうんうんざりしていない
think as a parent I mean isn't it tough
親として、私はそれが難しいと思います
to think that hey this device that I
このデバイスをちょっと考えて
bought for man I didn't but rhetorical
男のために買った
did I buy for my child so that I can
私ができるように子供のために買いましたか
kind of keep track of where they are and
どこにいるかを追跡し、
if they get lost in a mall I can find
彼らがモールで迷子になったら
them and to realize that there has been
それらとがあったことを認識するために
little to no security consideration it
セキュリティに関する考慮事項がほとんどない
feels like a violation by the company
会社による違反のように感じる
who manufactures this and that you are
誰がこれを製造していて、あなたが
collecting and allowing this data to be
このデータの収集と許可
accessible but putting no effort into
アクセス可能ですが、努力をしません
the actual security and protection and
実際のセキュリティと保護
and as a software developer myself that
そしてソフトウェア開発者として
is my first consideration yeah I've had
ええ、私の最初の考慮事項です
payment processing websites that come to
に来る支払い処理ウェブサイト
me and they said well why is it so
私と彼らはよく言った
expensive and I said because my first
高価だと言った
consideration is the security of the
考慮事項は、のセキュリティです
data of your customers and that has to
顧客のデータであり、
be the way it is yes you know there's so
そうであることがわかっている方法である
many comments I could make with this and
これで多くのコメントができました
it as a parent this this makes me feel
これは親としてこれが私に感じさせます
ill well yeah I mean I would love to
具合が悪い
have you know fun tech stuff for my kids
私の子供のための楽しい技術を知っていますか
and I mean oddly enough for Cyber Monday
サイバーマンデーには奇妙なことに
and Black Friday we were looking at
見ていたブラックフライデー
getting smartwatches for our kids ones
子供向けのスマートウォッチを入手する
that provided these kind of capabilities
この種の機能を提供した
but I couldn't pull the trigger because
トリガーを引くことができませんでした
I didn't recognize the brands they
私は彼らのブランドを認識しませんでした
weren't reputable sources they were good
評判の良い情報源ではなかった
deals yeah they weren't reputable names
ええ、彼らは評判の良い名前ではありませんでした
and I'm going hi can you trust this
そして、私はあなたがこれを信頼できますか？
right and I mean I hear stories like
そうだよ
this and I'm like you know what it's
これと私はあなたがそれが何であるかを知っているようです
time to go off the grid really good idea
グリッドを離れる時間は本当に良いアイデアです
it's a really good concept I mean in my
それは私が意味する本当に良いコンセプトです
line of work it would be really good for
仕事のライン
people with dementia or you know or
認知症の人またはあなたが知っているか
children it's really good to monitor the
子供たちはそれを監視するのは本当に良いです
safety of people who are vulnerable
脆弱な人々の安全
however these people are vulnerable and
しかし、これらの人々は脆弱であり、
it's really bad to exploit that I mean
悪用するのは本当に悪いことです
either with malicious intent
悪意を持って
or or just complacency right I don't
またはまたは単に自己満足の権利私はしません
like one when an idea is good like this
このようにアイデアが良いときのように
it needs to be followed up with the
フォローアップする必要があります
security that you know Robbie provides
ロビーが提供するセキュリティ
thank you now this brings up a like a
今、ありがとうございます
notification alert question within my
私の中の通知アラート質問
head like I'm listening to this I'm
私はこれを聞いているように頭
going and I'm thinking okay Robbie is a
行くと私は大丈夫だと思っていますロビーは
security guy maybe you can weigh in on
セキュリティ担当者は、多分あなたがで計量することができます
this if you have a company that quite
もしあなたがその会社を持っているなら
frankly doesn't care they've been
率直に言って、彼らは気にしていない
exposed for this issue and they don't
この問題のために公開され、彼らはしません
care for them it's about pumping out a
彼らの世話をするのは
device that is going to generate money
お金を生成するデバイス
for them and if it fails whatever
彼らのために、それが何でも失敗した場合
they'll just open it up under a new name
彼らは新しい名前でそれを開きます
and do it again as a parent who goes
そして行く親として再びそれを行う
this is a great option but they may not
これは素晴らしいオプションですが、そうでない場合があります
be watching for these kind of alerts
この種のアラートを監視している
yeah how as a parent do you catch the
ええ、親としてどのようにキャッチしますか
vulnerabilities with a device like this
このようなデバイスの脆弱性
if the company decides they're not going
会社が行かないと決めた場合
to alert you like yeah do it does the
ええ好きなようにあなたに警告するには
industry have an alert system where all
業界にはすべてのアラートシステムがあります
this stuff gets pushed out that a parent
このようなものは、親を押し出されます
can go I may not understand it but I
私はそれを理解できないかもしれませんが、私は行くことができます
know that this alert says that product
このアラートはその製品を示していることを知っています
all right I understand what you're
大丈夫私はあなたが何であるかを理解しています
saying like you know like when there's a
のようなあなたが知っているように言って
tainted produce at the grocery store and
食料品店で汚染された農産物
there's a huge recall I heard a recall
私はリコールを聞いた大きなリコールがあります
today and it's like the the product that
今日、それは製品のようなものです
was recalled expired yesterday so anyone
昨日失効したため、誰もがリコールされました
who bought it has already eaten it or
それを買った人はすでにそれを食べているか、
thrown it away anyways right what good
とにかくそれを捨てる
is that stand point for tech stuff from
技術スタッフの立場は
what parents can sign up for general
両親が一般にサインアップできるもの
alerts for this kind of stuff you know I
あなたが知っているこの種のものに関するアラート
don't know of one but I'm sure there is
知らないけど、きっとある
and and just backing up real quick I
そしてそして、本当に速くバックアップするだけです
don't want to take the assumption that
という仮定をしたくない
the people who manufacture the device
デバイスを製造する人々
don't care no I do I just I know it's a
気にしません
hypothetical but I just want to put that
仮説ですが、私はそれを置きたいだけです
out there that sometimes devices are put
時々デバイスが置かれることをそこに
out and and a lot of times with these
これらと多くの時間を
Chinese manufactured products it's like
中国製の製品
it's a manufactured thing that gets
製造されたものです
picked up by a third party in that third
そのサードでサードパーティによってピックアップ
party things hey this is a great idea
パーティーの事ちょっとこれは素晴らしいアイデアです
let's bring it to market and it all
市場に投入しましょう
happens quickly and it all happens
すぐに起こり、それはすべて起こります
without really the security guy
本当にセキュリティの男なしで
evaluating it guy gal evaluating the the
それを評価する
security implications and certainly this
セキュリティへの影響と確かにこれ
is a big one
大きなものです
especially as we look at things like
特に次のようなものを見るとき
Coppa and the protection of children and
コッパと子どもの保護と
the monitoring of children and now being
子供の監視と今
able to be exploit it's so easily I I
簡単に悪用できるII
don't know what to say I mean it's it's
何て言えばいいのかわからない
just it's bad practice all around but
ただそれはすべての周りの悪い習慣ですが、
we're feeding into it with the
私たちはそれにそれを供給しています
purchasing decisions that we make and I
私たちが行う購入決定と私
think you made a good decision Jeff to
あなたはジェフに良い決断をしたと思います
say I'm just not going to buy that but
私はそれを買うつもりはないが、
then what do you do if you want those
それからそれらがほしいとしたら何をしますか
kind of functionalities and maybe it's
機能の種類と多分それは
okay well sticking with brands that you
大丈夫あなたがブランドにこだわる
recognize and sticking with brands that
次のブランドを認識し、こだわり続ける
have child-safe policies perhaps there
おそらくそこに子供に安全な政策がある
must be some I know like ESET has
ESETが持っているような私が知っているものでなければなりません
parental controls that you can install
インストール可能なペアレンタルコントロール
on their phone if your kids have a
あなたの子供が持っている場合、彼らの携帯電話で
mobile device that's smart compatible
スマートに互換性のあるモバイルデバイス
has internet connectivity you can trace
トレースできるインターネット接続があります
it using geolocation and it's obviously
ジオロケーションを使用して、それは明らかに
I mean they're a security company it's
彼らはセキュリティ会社だということです
very well encrypted and and you are the
非常によく暗号化されており、あなたは
only person who has access to that data
そのデータにアクセスできる人のみ
so you know is that what we have to do
あなたは知っているので、私たちがしなければならないことです
it's not a cheap solution no it's not
それは安い解決策ではありません
and quite frankly it comes back to a lot
率直に言って、それは多くのことを思い出します
of times you pay for what yeah there you
ええ、そこに何を払うのか
go
行く
yeah I mean if you're you know for us we
ええ、あなたが私たちのために知っているなら
didn't pull the pin on these smart
これらのスマートでピンを引っ張らなかった
watches for the kids
子供向けの時計
yeah because hey was a great price but I
ええ、すごい値段だったからね
just I can't trust the name if I'm gonna
私はつもりだと私はちょうど名前を信頼することはできません
get a smart watch for my kids I'm gonna
子供のためにスマートウォッチを手に入れます
pay the two $300 for something from you
あなたから何かのために2つの300ドルを支払う
know Samsung or an Apple because I know
私が知っているので、サムスンやアップルを知っています
that they're gonna stand behind their
彼らは彼らの後ろに立っていること
security if something goes awry mmm-hmm
何かがうまくいかない場合のセキュリティmmm-hmm
it's it's a tricky time of year too
今年も大変な時期です
because everybody really does want to
誰もが本当にしたいので
get the newest and greatest in yeah so
ええで最新かつ最高のものを手に入れましょう
maybe this is a bit of a maybe this is
多分これは少しの多分これは
it maybe this is the PSA to the parents
多分これは両親へのPSAです
out there who have purchased these cheap
これらを安く購入した人がいます
devices from China that and just using
それを使用している中国のデバイス
this as the example it's like be mindful
これは例として、注意が必要です
okay this has happened this is happening
大丈夫、これが起こったこれは起こっている
you need to be you need to be protecting
保護する必要がある必要があります
your kids crazy
あなたの子供はクレイジー
big thanks to Roy W national community
ロイWナショナルコミュニティに大きな感謝
of viewers for submitting stories to us
ストーリーを提出してくれた視聴者の割合
this week thanks for watching the
今週見てくれてありがとう
category-five TV newsroom don't forget
カテゴリ5のテレビニュースルームもお忘れなく
to Like and subscribe for all your tech
すべての技術を「いいね」して購読する
news with a slight Linux bias and
Linuxにわずかな偏りがあるニュース
if you appreciate what we do become a
あなたが私たちがやることに感謝するなら
patron at patreon.com slash newsroom
patreon.comのパトロン、ニュースルームをスラッシュ
from the category-five TV newsroom I'm
カテゴリー5のテレビニュースルームから
Sasha Eggman and I'm Robbie Ferguson and
サーシャエッグマンと私はロビーファーガソンです
I'm Jeff West
ジェフウェストです
[Music]
[音楽]